Denise Weber

(330) 212-1204 dweber0001@gmail.com

Personal Summary

I am making a career change after working in the medical records field for many years. Due to offshoring, my entire team was laid off 11/2018, and I was given the opportunity to obtain an associate degree in software development, which I pursued wholeheartedly! I am now seeking an opportunity with a great company in which I can integrate my prior work history with the developer skills I have obtained for a long term position. Skills I bring: Independent learner, strong multitasker, time-management skills, long-term remote worker, persistence, problem solver, positive and optimistic attitude, passionate about learning/growing/technology.

Work Experience

Quality Improvement Specialist (Remote position)

MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN

October 2008 to November 2018

Duties: Drive Service Delivery excellence for assigned customers via compliance with Quality Program utilizing live audits and positive communication. Perform monthly assigned quality audits. Due to offshoring, my entire team was laid off November 2018.

Manager, Service Delivery (Remote position)

MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN

July 2007 to October 2008

Managed 5 Supervisors and staff of MTs and QA staff. Daily Goals: Train/Support Supervisors to achieve workflow and quality goals, address stat issues, hiring, training, PMP/PIP, termination. Responsibilities: Performance of Supervisors, MTs and QA staff in attaining TATs, quality, and customer service goals for the 105 hospitals/clinics in our book of business. Company restructure resulted in elimination of all Manager Roles; was retained with company in Quality Improvement Specialist role.

QA Manager/Audit Supervisor (Remote position)

MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN

Managed 32 FTE QA Specialists. Developed QA plan to address quality issues/TAT and increase QA production. Promoted 06/2006: Audit Supervisor N Region, part of new national team. Duties: Develop, interview, hire, train team of 15 auditors. Lotus Notes Audit DB administrator. Developed training materials, led webinars, trainer for new auditors, liaison for database users. Promoted to Manager, SD.

Education

Associate Degree - Software Development

Sinclair Community College - Dayton, OH

April 2019 to December 2020

Graduated with Honors. Cumulative GPA of 3.41

Certificates: • IT Fundamentals 08/2020 • Fast Track Programming 12/2020

MModal Management Program - Harvard Business School August 2007 to October 2008 Leadership/Coaching, Managing Performance Problems, PMP/PIP, Assessing Performance, Leading Virtual High-Performing Teams, Setting Goals, Delegating, Managing Crises, Time Management.

Portfolio: https://dweber0001.github.io/ GitHub: http://github.com/dweber0001

Skills

- ASP.NET (1 year)
- CSS3 (2 years)
- OOP
- FLASK/JINJA2
- GITHUB

- BOOTSTRAP
- HTML5 (2 years)
- ReactJS
- HEROKU
- ORACLE SQL/MyS
- C# (1 year)
- JAVASCRIPT (1 year)
- NPM
- MongoDB
- DATABASE DESIGN ERD

Additional Skills

- Medical records terminology, auditing, editing, reporting, research (10+ years)
- Supervisor/Manager; team building, problem-solving, coaching, leading virtual teams, communication/time management, assessing performance, managing performance issues, PMP/PIP, hiring, training, setting goals. (5 years)
- MS Office products, research/analysis, small business accounting, QuickBooks.